Stop killing them.
It's all my fault.
For resisting the Great Japanese Imperial Army,
this woman will die for your crimes.
No.
She's the daughter of my savior.
Please let her live.
Help!
She's just a child who knows nothing.
Kill me.
No!
No, no.
Bastard!
Meixiang.
I had a nightmare again.
Come here.
Did I say something strange just now?
You were speaking Japanese just now.
We've been married for twenty years.
I don't even know who you are.
You have to explain it clearly to me today.
Who are you exactly?
Tell me!
My real name is Zhou Tiexiong.
I was born in Fengtian, Northeast China.
My parents died when I was little.
I was just an orphan,
living by begging on the streets every day.
I don't know if I had good luck or bad luck,
a Japanese veteran adopted me
and made me his adopted son.
He provided me with food and clothes,
and taught me how to read and write.
I once thought
that I had really gone to heaven.
Until the day I came of age,
he said he wanted to hold a coming-of-age ceremony for me,
and sent me to the Japanese military camp as a soldier.
From then on,
the nightmare began.
The Japanese army trained us
by using civilians as bayonet targets.
Many people died in front of me with their intestines ripped out.
They also forced me
to undergo such courage-building training,
saying it was for the Emperor's holy war.
I couldn't take it anymore,
so I had to play dead to leave the Japanese army
and flee all the way to the west,
wanting to get as far away from this battlefield as possible.
Before I knew it,
I arrived at Sandaoyuan.
When I was about to starve to death,
Shangguan Bao appeared.
He saved my life.
And later,
later I met you.
Since then,
I didn't want to run anymore.
I wanted to stay
and spend the rest of my life with you.
So,
the Japanese man who forced you,
he came to the chief's birthday banquet?
That's him.
I have been hiding from him,
but I still fell into his hands.
I don't want to lose you.
I can't lose you,
but I have absolutely no choice.
Just tell me,
do you have the chief's blood on your hands?
No, absolutely not.
I swear.
I was deceived.
I never thought of harming the chief.
Meixiang, listen to me.
I'll trust you one more time.
I'll listen to you.
I'll take Xiaoni away from here.
But you can't keep making mistakes.
You absolutely cannot make any more mistakes.
Don't worry.
Once I get rid of Tianyuan Zhengxiong's threat,
I will definitely correct my mistakes
and kill those lurking Japanese spies.
For the sake of you and our daughter,
I have to be a good man for once.
Master.
Take a look at this first.
Isn't this Cai Zhen?
It says Communist Party.
Is there a mistake?
This was issued
from Major General Kurokawa's headquarters.
The woman in the picture
is Cai Zhen, the Communist
who participated in the sabotage in Fuyang.
I didn't expect Cai Zhen to be so complicated.
She should be
a Communist hiding within the Nationalist army.
The Communist Party and the Nationalist Party seem to be allies,
but they've been fighting openly and secretly.
Major,
can we use this
to make a fuss?
You're very smart, Kiriyama.
I've already had someone start working on it.
I want to use Zhang Gongyan to get rid of Cai Zhen.
Even if we can't get rid of her,
we can weaken the Communist Party's power in Shanzhou.
Brilliant, Major.
Cai Zhen.
Are my eyes playing tricks on me?
Is this really Major Cai Zhen on here?
Yes.
It also says here
she is a Communist operating in Luoyang.
This woman is actually a Communist.
She hid so well,
actually infiltrating the Juntong.
Commander Zhang.
The Communists are best at two things:
espionage infiltration
and propaganda for the united front.
We've been in Shanzhou for so long,
and nothing goes smoothly.
Actually,
it's the Communists causing trouble.
If it weren't for Cai Baozi, who was in charge of communication,
getting into trouble,
those 100,000 swordsmen would have been theirs.
Do you think this wanted poster
is enough to prove it?
Commander.
Look,
the Japanese wouldn't for no reason
put out a wanted poster for a woman
and accuse her of being a Communist.
Actually,
I've investigated this woman privately.
She and a Communist named Cai Baozi
are very close.
She has helped him time and again.
I think she is one.
It's this woman who ruined our plan,
snatching the fat piece of meat that was the Independent Brigade
right out of our mouths.
Use your brain
and tell me everything you know.
The Theater Commander
wants to drive the Communists out of Western Henan.
This is a well-known fact.
But the Communists have always been
careful and cautious.
There isn't enough evidence.
Commander Zhang.
If you catch Cai Zhen
and use her as solid evidence,
wouldn't it be a great achievement?
If I catch Cai Zhen,
not only can I claim credit from my superiors,
but I can also take personal revenge. Right.
Wonderful.
Absolutely wonderful.
Gather the troops
and arrest Cai Zhen.
Yes.
It feels so good to be back in my own seat.
The matter I asked you to investigate,
how is it going?
All clues point to one person,
Zhang Gongyan.
He is also the only one with the motive
to kill our father.
Commander Zhang.
I just got out of prison not long ago.
I haven't had time to visit you yet.
Why did you bring these people here
to make trouble?
Brigade Commander Cui, you're pretty tough.
What happened in the past was all a misunderstanding.
Just calm down.
Today we are here to arrest
the Communist spy Cai Zhen.
What did you say?
Cai Zhen is a Communist?
Commander Zhang,
you can't make this kind of joke.
She's from the Military Statistics Bureau.
Major Cai, nice disguise.
Unfortunately, you were careless
and the Japanese found out first.
Then what do you want, Commander Zhang?
I want to invite you to be a guest in my prison.
Then tell me
what conspiracy the Communists are planning.
Take her away.
Wait.
What,
Commander Cui?
Are you going to plead for a Communist?
Commander Zhang,
you know that I
have always hated Communists the most.
This woman
made me stay in jail for two days
and suffer a lot.
I have to teach her a lesson.
Leave her to me.
Okay.
I'll give you a chance.
Miss Cai, let's go.
Comrade Wenpei.
You two, get her out of the city quickly.
Okay.
What about you?
How will you explain this to him?
Knock me out.
Well, Comrade Wenpei,
how can I do that?
Yeah, right.
I told you to knock me out.
Did you hear me?
Go. Hurry up and go.
I thought using a tiger to drive away a wolf was brilliant enough,
but I didn't expect to see such a good show.
I'll get rid of him.
Brigade Commander, wake up.
Give it to me. Come.
Brigade Commander.
With Zhang Gongyan around,
Cui Wenkui is like a tiger in a cage.
No matter how capable he is, he can't use it,
so he is not worth our worry.
The ones we need to eliminate
are the most troublesome Communists.
Through this forest,
We'll be at our liaison station soon.
Someone is tailing us.
Don't look back.
Are they Zhang Gongyan's men?
I can't see clearly.
They're all in plain clothes.
I can't tell who they are.
They can't be Zhang Gongyan's men.
On Chinese soil,
who else would sneak around like this
but Japanese spies?
Out of the frying pan
and into the fire.
It seems the reason for all the trouble in Shanzhou
is Tianyuan Zhengxiong's doing.
Go find Baozi quickly.
Our place is no longer safe.
Okay.
Wenpei, why are you back?
We need to evacuate immediately.
It's no longer safe here.
What's wrong?
Japanese spies are nearby.
We must leave now.
Bring all the documents.
Okay.
Hurry, there's no time. Let's go.
Let's go, Wenpei. Let's go.
Hurry, let's go.
Hurry!
Baozi, take out the document quickly.
You guys take the document and leave.
Baozi and I will distract the enemy
to cover your retreat.
This document contains
the list of our organization's activities
and future operation plans.
You must protect it well.
Never let it fall into anyone else's hands.
Don't worry, you guys be careful.
Stay safe. Go now.
Take care.
- Go.
Welcome to Qinfoyegou.
Boss.
These two are my distinguished guests.
Show them some respect.
Let me tell you.
Stepping into my territory
is like entering a maze.
Not to mention the Japanese,
even the locals
would get lost here.
Boss Huo,
thanks to your help today.
Otherwise, we...
Otherwise,
you really would have become ghosts under the Japanese swords.
What the hell are you talking about?
No matter how fierce the Japanese are,
didn't you still come back alive?
Second Brother.
I didn't expect to be so lucky either.
Just thinking about the Japanese makes me angry.
My wound still hurts.
But then again, Second Brother,
when I ran back,
didn't I scare you too?
You really are a lucky guy.
Miss Cai, you really have no idea.
Recently,
my second brother has been tracking the Japanese.
We didn't expect to save you halfway.
Tell me,
what is this?
Destiny, right?
Destiny.
Boss Huo,
you saved us today.
I am extremely grateful.
Don't mention it.
But aren't you afraid that the Qinglong Stronghold people
will come to make trouble for you,
saying you are harboring a murderer?
Harboring what murderer?
Let me tell you.
The people in Qinfoyegou
are all extremely wicked.
We don't care about one more murderer.
Let me tell you guys,
don't underestimate me.
Although I, Huo Lang, don't have piercing eyes,
I am not blind either.
After the Big Boss died,
everyone said Cai Baozi
was the murderer.
Even my eldest niece took a shot at him.
But as for me, I don't believe it.
Why?
I've been through life and death with Cai Baozi.
What kind of person he is,
I know best.
Saying he covets the Big Boss's position,
nonsense.
Boss Huo,
I have a new understanding of you today.
Okay.
Stop being polite.
I haven't finished speaking yet.
The boss is dead.
We must avenge him.
We need to find out who the killer is.
I already sent someone
to sneak into Qinglong Stronghold secretly.
The messenger said
that He Xiaobian,
since he took over the boss's position,
has been acting weird,
sneaking down the mountain several times
to meet someone.
He Xiaobian.
Who did he go to meet?
They were too far away.
The person following him couldn't see clearly.
Boss Huo,
do you suspect
that Shangguan Bao's death is related to He Xiaobian?
I'm not confused, am I?
All right, all right.
Let's go inside and talk.
We need to discuss what to do next.
Let's go.
Xiaoliu,
hurry up and make some tea.
Didn't you see we have distinguished guests?
You have no tact at all.
This...
Meixiang.
Keep this for the journey.
We have enough travel expenses.
You will need this.
Keep it for yourself.
Uncle, it's about time.
Yinger.
I leave Aunt Meixiang and Xiaoni in your care.
Don't worry.
I've got this.
I'm counting on you.
Dad.
Let's go.
Let's go, Nier.
Get on.
Careful.
You go first.
Aunt.
Advisor.
Old man.
Look after the house well.
Wait for us to come back.
Go.
Stop this carriage.
Catch the people in it.
Go.
Catch this carriage.
Bastard.
Meixiang, Ni'er.
I hope you have made it out of the mountain safely.
Speed up to catch up with them.
And get ahead of them.
Yes.
Go.
I can't use the men from Qinglong Stronghold.
Now I can only rely on Huo Lang's power
to get rid of Tianyuan Zhengxiong.
Wait a minute.
Auntie, the city gate is just ahead.
Once you enter the city,
you and Xiaoni will be safe.
What are you doing, Ying?
I can't go with you.
I must return to Qinglong Fort.
What are you doing?
Didn't you agree with your uncle
to come with us?
Qinglong Fort is not safe.
If Uncle didn't say that,
would you have been willing to leave the mountain?
With the enemy approaching,
I have to stay with my brothers.
Sister,
didn't you say
you'd protect me?
Silly girl.
I'll come find you guys soon.
Remember,
take good care of your mother.
Ying.
Miss Cai.
Here's a leopard skin rug for you.
It's very warm.
Chief Huo, I don't need this.
No, this cave is too damp.
With your delicate skin,
it wouldn't be good if you caught a cold.
Is the murderer of the chief
really He Xiaobian?
Everything is in chaos right now.
What should we do next?
Miss Cai.
I am a person
who can't hide anything.
I really like you.
I hope you can stay here,
eat well, sleep well,
and stay for good.
To be honest,
if we were about the same age,
I would definitely beg you
to be my wife.
I appreciate your kindness, Chief Huo.
You really don't need to. Just accept it.
Second Brother.
Let's drink.
No, this...
Miss Cai, no, just take it.
Drink.
What drink?
I'm talking here.
Baozi.
I know you are upset now
and anxious to get out.
Seeing that the united front mission was about to be completed,
I never expected it to turn out like this.
We still underestimated the enemy.
But this is the most urgent moment.
We can't panic.
What should we do next?
We must find out the real killer of Shangguan Bao.
Otherwise, all our previous work will be in vain.
Without the trust of the swordsmen,
what's the point of a united front?
Chief.
What's wrong?
Chief,
someone sent a message by throwing a knife.
Bring it here.
Miss Cai, this...
Just right.
Take a look.
No, what does this say?
Masao Tahara.
Yidaoyuan Underground Courtyard, oil shop.
This is great.
We finally caught the fox's tail.
Boss Huo, you did a good job.
No, what's good about it?
I didn't do it.
You didn't do it?
Second Brother.
Wasn't this note written by one of our men?
No, this...
No, look at this knife.
Is it from our stronghold?
Could it be that Masao Tahara
has set a trap
to lure us out of the mountains?
Didn't you say Qin Foye Gully
is hard for others to find?
Right.
Except for the people from our Eighteen Poles Mountain,
who could sneak in?
This...
Don't worry. As long as you're here,
no one can touch a hair on your head.
To be honest, staying here makes me uncomfortable all over.
How about we call the brothers out
to stretch our legs?
Boss Huo, just give the word.
Alright.
Wang Shi'er.
I'm thinking,
as long as Masao Tahara is not eliminated,
our Sandaoyuan won't have peace.
Whether it's true or false this time,
since we know his hiding place,
let's pick a few capable brothers and make a trip.
What do you think?
Second Brother, I've been waiting for you to say that.
I'll go right now. All right.
Go immediately.
If it's true,
I will tear him into pieces this time.
Takeshita, how is it?
Tahara,
after my repeated examination and scrutiny,
this is just an ordinary map.
There is nothing valuable on it.
Takeshita,
you are an expert in this field.
I went through a lot of trouble to get these two maps.
You must observe them carefully.
Make sure you don't miss anything.
Tahara Masao sure knows how to pick a spot.
Hiding here.
Second Brother.
I'm familiar with this place.
You are?
My aunt
is from Zhang Village right here.
How many villages
and houses are here,
I know them all.
We've been walking all this way,
and I haven't seen any villages
or houses or anything like that.
Miss Cai,
on this plateau,
the villages are all underground.
The villagers live in subterranean courtyards.
Wenpei.
Seeing trees but no village, seeing a village but no houses,
hearing voices but seeing no people,
that describes subterranean courtyards.
Yes, yes, that's right.
Brothers,
hide the horses well in a bit.
Second Brother.
I'll lead the way.
How about I lead?
I'll lead. I'll lead. I'll lead.
Major,
Huo Lang brought his men here.
Don't panic.
Pack your things and come with me.
Yes, sir.
It should be this way.
Probably.
I remember it's this way, Second Brother.
Right here.
Look.
I told you it was here.
Attention, everyone.
This is the entrance to the Dikeng Courtyard.
Once we go in,
you must stay close.
It's very big inside.
If you're not careful,
you'll get lost.
Do I need you to tell me?
Let me tell you.
I made a promise to Miss Cai.
We will capture Masao Tahara alive.
If you embarrass me,
I'll kill you.
Don't worry, Second Brother.
I'll find someone to ask later.
Fellow villager, let me ask you something.
Don't run! Catch him!
What are you doing? Are you crazy?
Why are you running?
I saw you all carrying knives.
You're either robbers or the security corps.
If I didn't run, I'd just be waiting for you to rob me.
This...
You kid.
Let me tell you,
you've misunderstood.
We are good people.
Look.
We are the famous
Qinfoyegou Swordsmen.
What?
You are the bandits from the mountain?
No.
What nonsense are you talking about? Enough.
Are you asking for a beating?
Enough. What are you doing?
Look how big the reputation of your Qinfoyegou is.
You frightened the civilians like this.
Yes, Miss Cai.
We, the people of Qinfoyegou,
just have bad tempers.
We have never done anything wicked.
Yes, Miss Cai.
I was a bit anxious just now.
I was just trying to catch the Japanese spies.
I didn't know my limits.
How about this.
I'll ask again.
Speak nicely and ask again.
I'll be nicer. Well...
Sir.
Do you know where the oil shop is?
Oil shop?
What oil shop?
We need to go to the oil shop for some business.
If you know the way,
could you point us in the right direction?
Go through that hole,
pass through these two alleys,
and there's a big tree inside.
It's right under it.
Thank you.
Look at you.
You can't even ask for directions.
Miss Cai had to do it herself.
You've completely disgraced Qin Foyegou.
Second Brother.
When I catch the Japanese spies later,
I'll win back our face, okay?
You take the lead.
You guys block this entrance.
Don't let Tianyuan Zhengxiong escape.
Did you hear me?
Yes.
Let's go.
Wenpei,
don't you think something is wrong?
We rushed all the way here,
but didn't see any visible or hidden sentries.
This doesn't look like a Jap hideout.
I think so too.
I actually feel
there's something wrong with that middle-aged man.
I didn't notice it.
He just looked like an ordinary villager here.
My instinct has never been wrong.
But what is the problem?
Keep your voices down.
We might alert the Japs.
I think that guy Tian is hiding here.
Brothers,
follow me later.
Let's split up and search.
We must capture that guy Tian alive.
Go.
Is anyone here?
Nobody.
Oh no, Second Brother.
We've searched several pit yards.
Did we make a mistake?
I was wondering what was wrong.
When we mentioned
catching Japanese spies just now,
that middle-aged man wasn't scared at all.
He is definitely not an ordinary villager.
I was just trying to catch Japanese spies.
I didn't handle it well.
He is the Japanese spy.
Our brothers are in danger. Let's go back quickly.
Hurry! No, this...
Go.
If I catch this Japanese spy,
I will definitely burn him alive.
Tahara Masao must have received the news
and ran away with his men.
You shouldn't have stopped me just now.
I would have beaten that Japanese devil to death.
All right, stop talking.
Hurry up and chase them. Everyone, charge.
Go, chase them.
Chief Huo, don't be reckless.
Tahara Masao is not that simple.
Let's hurry up and follow them,
in case they have an accident. Go.
Over there.
Major, the person who was pursuing us just now
looked like Cai Baozi.
That's right, it's him.
Didn't he fall off the cliff and die?
It seems he is really lucky.
Major, we only have a few men left.
Where can we go?
We can't stay in Shanzhou City anymore.
But,
as long as we have the map,
we still have a chance to turn the tables.
Follow me to find someone.
Who?
Boss.
A friend of yours is outside asking to see you.
Since when do I have friends?
All my friends are in the stronghold.
He says his surname is Tian.
He's Boss Tian from Shanzhou City,
who sells oil, salt, and cloth.
Tianyuan Zhengxiong.
Didn't Huo Lang kill him?
How many people? How are they dressed?
Six people, one carriage,
and they are carrying goods.
Right, I remember now.
I asked them to come.
Let's go. I'll go take a look with you.
Let's go.
Boss He,
that's him.
Boss Tian, long time no see.
How have you been?
Thanks to you, Boss He, I've been doing well.
Your Qinglong Stronghold
is truly guarded like an iron fortress.
I came to visit you, yet you had to come in person.
I'm really sorry about that.
How dare you come here?
Do you have a death wish?
It's exactly because I want to live
that I came here.
With your protection, I'll be perfectly fine.
Aren't you afraid I'll tie you up?
Go ahead.
Tying me up is like tying yourself up.
Masao Tahara, this is Qinglong Stronghold,
not the Japanese army's territory.
Chief He.
I know.
It's just a matter of time.
Don't tell me Chief He
doesn't even have this little foresight.
Mr. Tian, please.
Thank you.
Bring in all Chief He's gifts.
Yes. Let's go.
He,
how dare you deceive me?
Tianyuan Zhengxiong,
what makes you say that?
The experts have examined it,
and that map is clearly just an ordinary painting.
But you kept saying it was a treasure map.
How do you explain this?
This is Shangguan Bao's
gold mine treasure map that he kept hidden in the secret room.
As for you not being able to decipher it,
that's your problem.
Instead of shouting here,
why don't you go back and let your experts take another look?
The experts said
it's just an ordinary painting.
Do you think I still dare to lie to you now?
Not necessarily.
Let me tell you, He,
don't think that just because you gave me the map,
you're safe and sound.
Then what else do you want?
If that map can't be deciphered,
you won't have a good time.
You still dare to threaten me?
I am already all alone.
I'm not afraid of you anymore.
All alone?
Really?
Chibei-kun.
Ni'er.
You...